我可以从地狱把你拉出来 我也可以再把你送回去
I dragged you out of hell. I can throw you back in.
你该对我尊敬点
You should show me some respect.
在未来的几个月里 你要做出更多的抉择
In the coming months, you will have more decisions to make.
迪恩 那里是怎么样的
Dean, what was it like?
你指地狱
What, hell?
我不知道 我眼前一片漆黑
I don't know. i-i must have blacked it out.
我什么都不记得
I don't remember a damn thing.
这是尤瑞尔 一位专家
This is uriel, a specialist.
哪方面的专家
Specializing in what?
你们俩赶快离开这里
Both of you, you need to leave this town immediately.
为什么
Why?
因为我们可能要摧毁这里
Because we're about to destroy it.
你活到现在的唯一原因 萨姆 温彻斯特
The only reason you're still alive, sam winchester,
就是你对我们还是有帮助的
Is because you've been useful.
这一刻将成为历史 我就把你变成尘土
The moment that ceases to be true, then I will turn you to dust.
问问迪恩 地狱是怎么样的
Ask dean what he remembers from hell.
有人吗
Hello?
谁在那里
Is anybody there?
你好吗
Um, hello?
[邪恶力量 第4季第8集]
这一点也不和常理 迪恩
It just doesn't make any sense, dean.
为什么尤瑞尔让我问你地狱是怎么样的 可你却不记得
I mean, why would uriel tell me you remembered hell if you didn't?
可能他是个傻逼 不过可能这事和他有点关系
Maybe because he's a prick … might have something to do with it.
只是可能 但他是个天使
Maybe, but he's still an angel.
对，一个要把这里夷为平地的天使
Yeah, an angel who was ready to level an entire town.
我不知道他的做法 - 伙计你太激动了
Look, i don't know what … radical.
还需要什么么
What else can I get you guys?
不用了
Uh, i think we're good. yeah?
想不想试试炸脆骨或咖喱辣墨西哥菜
You want to try a couple of fryer bombs or a chipotle chili changa?
不用 我们吃饱了
No, no, we're still good.
很好
Okay, awesome.
萨姆 老实说 我不知道为什么尤瑞尔要告诉你他的做法
Sam, honestly, I have no idea why uriel told you what he did, okay?
好的
Right.
什么
What? okay.
很好
Fine.
你看着我的眼睛 告诉我
Then look me in the eye and tell me you.
你不记得在地狱里发生什么了
Don't remember a thing from your time down under.
我什么也不记得
I don't remember a thing from my time down under.
我真不记得了 萨姆
I don't remember, sam!
我只是想帮你
Look, dean, I just want to help.
我做了什么你都知道 就这些
You know everything I do. okay? that's all there is.
要不要来点甜点
Outstanding. dessert time?
我说的对不
Huh? am I right?
伙计 听着
Dude. listen, bros.
你应该试试我们的超级无敌冰淇淋
You have got to try our ice cream extreme.
是超级无敌的
It's extreme.
不用 谢谢
Uh, no extremities, please.
买 埋单
Just the … check?
很好 谢谢
All right, awesome. thanks.
我们现在去哪里
All right, so, where do we go from here?
不知道
I'm not sure.
最近好像发生了一系列事
Uh, looks like it's been pretty quiet lately.
没有任何征兆
No signs of demon activity, no omens or portents I can see.
这次是好消息
That's good news for once.
对
Yeah,
就是一些不和逻辑的怪事
Just the typical smattering of crank ufo.
可能是幽灵的复仇
Sightings and one possible vengeful spirit.
看看这个
Here, check this out. uh…
在华盛顿的水泥城
Up in concrete, washington,
目击者说看到一个鬼
Eyewitness reports of a ghost that's been.
在女生浴室里偷窥
Haunting the showers of a women's health facility.
受害者说那个鬼把她从一段楼梯上推下来
The victim claims that the ghost threw her down a flight of stairs.
我觉得你很感兴趣
I can see you're very interested.
女人 浴室
Women, showers.
我们要去拯救这些人
We got to save these people.
鬼要找我 我一点都不感到奇怪
I'm not surprised the spirit world chose to make contact with me.
我是某些
I'm something of a…
灵媒
Natural sensitive.
我能感觉到你 坎迪斯
I can sense that about you, candace, that whole…
那些关于通灵的事
Sensitive thing.
你会怎么命名你的书
So, what did you say you're calling your book?
我想叫
Oh, well, um…
我想用
Well, the working title is…
凶鬼恶灵
"supernatural."
我周游全国 收集一些故事
Yeah, i've been crossing the country, gathering stories like yours.
告诉我你的遭遇
But, anyways, you were telling me about your encounter.
好 当我一看到鬼魂 是我在跑步的是后
Yes. well once I saw the apparition, that's when I started to run.
你说鬼魂在追你
And you said the ghost chased you?
不止这样 他还知道我的名字
Not just that. it knew my name.
一直在喊着阿姆斯特朗太太 阿姆斯特朗太太
It kept yelling, "mrs. armstrong! mrs. armstrong!"
在那时我就撞到台阶摔倒了
And that's when I hit the stairs and fell.
你自己摔倒还是那鬼魂推了你
You fell? the ghost didn't push you.
我不知道
Oh, i don't … I don't know.
我猜是他推我的
I mean, i think it did.
有可能
Maybe.
你有没有觉得被伤害到 比如被暴力或是
Did you feel like it meant to hurt you, like it was violent, or…
那是个鬼 我真幸运我还活着
It was a ghost. I'm lucky to be alive.
总之 我觉得这事挺邪乎的时候 我就在楼梯下面了
Anyway, i was at the bottom of the stairs, and that's when it got weird.
它扶我起来
It helped me up.
什么？
Say again?
它扶我起来
Yeah. it helped me up.
嘴里还不断的嘟囔着 别告诉我妈妈
And it kept saying over and over, "please, don't tell my mom."
没错 真够怪的
Yeah, that's weird.
发现什么了没有
Well, you pick up anything?
浴室里和外面EMF探测器都没有反应
No emf in the shower or anywhere else.
这屋子没什么问题
This house is clean.
恩 我一点都不奇怪
Yeah. I'm not surprised.
我倒是能体会几分这种的感觉
I kind of got the feeling back there that crazy pushed mrs.
疯狂的把阿姆斯特朗夫人推下楼梯
Armstrong down the stairs.
我得告诉你 我对你很失望
I got to tell you, I'm pretty disappointed.
你总想去拯救没穿衣服的女人
You wanted to save naked women.
我的确要去拯救一些没穿衣服的女人
Damn right I wanted to save some naked women.
快点 伙计们 抓住他
Come on, guys, get him!
抓住他
I got him! I got him!
快跑
Run, forrest, run!
抱歉 迪恩 我不觉得这儿会有什么事发生
Sorry, dean, but I don't think anything's going on around here.
我为什么要去那边看看
How the hell was I supposed to get a look at it?
它从后面抓住我并把我逼入窘境
It grabbed me from behind and threw me into a tree!
有活干了
Something's going on.
冷静点 伙计 我理解你被吓到了
Yeah, okay, gus. I understand you got shook up.
换成谁都会如此
Anyone would be.
但是为什么你不认为这不是熊干的好事呢
But don't you think it … don't you think it had to be a bear?
当我看见脚印我就会知道这是熊的足迹
I know a damn bear track when I see one!
不过刚才根本没有留下熊的足迹
This thing didn't leave bear tracks!
它的脚很大 是个大脚怪
Its feet were huge! now, gus … it was bigfoot, hal … the bigfoot!
伙计 你的话没道理可言
Gus, you're not talking sense here.
有个大脚怪在那里 妈的 他就是个混蛋
There's a bigfoot out there, damn it, and he's a son of a bitch!
打扰一下
Excuse us.
- FBI - 什么事
- FBI. - What?
我们来这里是调查
Yes, sir. we're here about the…
调查大脚怪
That. about bigfoot?
没错
That's right.
先生 能不能准确的告诉我们前面发生了什么
Sir, can you tell me exactly where this happened?
没问题
Yes, i can.
这个小镇怎么了
What the hell's going on in this town?
首先不是真正的鬼魂 现在又是大脚怪
First there's a ghost that's not real and now a bigfoot sighting?
每个称职的猎人都知道大脚怪是恶作剧
Well, every hunter worth his salt knows bigfoot's a hoax.
也许有人把古钱币放进这个镇的供水系统
Well, maybe somebody's pumping lsd into the town water supply.
好吧
Okay.
你猜这是什么
What do you suppose made that?
这个
That, uh…
是一个大脚印
Is a big foot.
好吧
Okay.
大脚怪闯进这酒馆来弄点酒喝
So, what … bigfoot breaks into a liquor store, jonesing for some hooch?
意大利苦杏酒和爱尔兰奶酪
Amaretto and irish cream.
他看起来酒量不行
He's a girl-drink drunk.
来看看这里
Hey. check this out.
他把整架的色情杂志都拿走了？
He took the whole porno rack?
好吧 我又得说一次
Well, i'll say it again.
这个镇到底他妈的怎么了
What the hell is going on in this town?
我一无所获
I got nothing.
看起来是恶作剧 对吧
It's got to be a joke, right?
一些巨型猩猩穿着暴徒装
Some big-ass mother in a gorilla suit?
或是大脚怪
Or it's a bigfoot.
看起来是对酒精和性爱有瘾
You know, and he's some kind of a alcoholo-porno addict.
像深山老林版的杜楚尼（X档案演员 曾沉溺性爱接受治疗）
Kind of like a deep-woods duchovny.
一个小孩子的大胸亚洲女郎杂志
A little young for busty asian beauties.
这出像不像电影「大脚哈利」里的
What's this, like a "harry and the hendersons" deal?
你好
Hello?
你好啊
Hello!
我们能
Um, could we…
你的父母在不在家呢
You know what? are your parents home?
不在
Nope.
不 不
No. no.
你有没有看见一个真实的毛茸茸的
Have you seen a really, really furry…
他闯祸了？
Is he in trouble?!
没有
No.
当然没有
No, no, no.
一点都没有
Not at all.
我们只能想来确认下他没事
We just … we wanted to make sure he was okay.
对头
Exactly.
他是我的泰迪熊
He's my teddy bear.
我觉得他病了
I think he's sick.
太吃惊了
Amazing.
你知道么 我们
'cause you know what? We…
是
Are, uh…
泰迪熊的医生
Teddy bear doctors.
真的吗
Really?
你们来帮我看看他吧
Can you please take a look at him?
那是当然
Sure. sure. yeah.
他在我的卧室里 脾气很暴躁
He's in my bedroom. he's pretty grumpy.
泰迪？
Teddy?
这里有两个好好的医生来看你哦
There's some nice doctors here to see you.
关上那该死的门
Close the friggin' door!
明白我的意思了吧
See what I mean?
我一直就想要一个大大的 活生生的 会说话的泰迪熊
All I ever wanted was a teddy which was big, real, and talked.
但是他现在总是很难过 不是那种疼得难过
But now he's sad all the time … not "ouch" sad,
但是是那种头痛得难过 说奇怪的话，闻起来像流脓了。
But ouch-in-the-head sad … says weird stuff, and smells like the bus.
嗯，小姑娘…奥德丽
Um, little girl… audrey!
奥德丽
Audrey.
你的泰迪熊是怎么变成活生生的了
How exactly did your teddy become real?
我许了个愿望
I wished for it.
你许了个愿
You wished for it?
在许愿池边
At the wishing well.
看看吧
Look at this.
你相信这种鬼话
You believe this crap?
不全信
Not really.
这是个可怕的世界
It is a terrible world.
我为什么在这里
Why am I here?!
为了茶话会
For tea parties!
茶话会
Tea parties?
就为了这个吗
Is that all there is?
奥德丽 让我们单独谈谈 好吗
Audrey, give us a second, okay?
好的
Okay.
我们要
Are we…
我们应该…
Should we…
我们要杀了这个泰迪熊吗
Are we gonna kill this teddy bear?
怎么做 我们射死它 还是烧死它
How? do we shoot it, burn it?
我也不知道 双管齐下
I don't know. both?
我们如何知道那会不会有效
How do we even know that's gonna work?
我可不想管那脾气坏又逊毙了的巨型泰迪熊 是啊
I don't want some giant, flaming, pissed-off teddy on our hands. yeah.
还有 我觉得那熊不是真的 你知道我是什么意思
Besides, i get the feeling that the bear isn't really the, you know,
关键问题就在这
Core problem here.
奥德丽 你的父母在哪
Audrey. where are your parents?
我妈妈希望他们在巴厘岛 所以我想他们应该就在巴厘岛
My mom wished they were in bali, so I think they're in bali.
好的 那么
Okay, well…
我很抱歉告诉你这些 但是
I'm really sorry to have to break this to you, but…
你的泰迪熊病了
Your bear is sick.
是的 它 它得了
Yeah, he's … he's got…
棒棒糖综合症
Lollipop disease.
对于他这样的熊是很罕见的
It's not uncommon for a bear his size.
但是 要知道 这可是传染的
But, see, it's really contagious.
是的 所以 有没有什么人 比方说一个大人
Yeah, so, is there someone, maybe a grown-up,
在我们为它治疗的时候可以陪着你
That you can stay with while we treat him?
赫丽太太住在这条街尾
Mrs. hurley lives down the street.
太棒了 好的 是啊 那真好
Perfect. good, yeah, good.
嗯 我们希望你去那里呆几天 好吗 好的
Uh, we'd like you to stay there for a few days, okay? okay.
哦 还有 奥德丽 那个许愿池在哪里
Oh, and, audrey? where is this wishing well?
你认为会奏效吗
Think it works?
你有更好的解释那里为什么有那么一个泰迪熊吗
Got a better explanation for teddy back there?
好吧 只有这一个办法了
Well, there's one way to find out.
你要许什么愿
What are you gonna wish for?
别吵
Shh!
不可以说出来的
Not supposed to tell.
谁叫了一份意大利加墨西哥胡椒三明治
Somebody order a footlong italian with jalapeno.
那是我点的
That'd be me.
哥们儿 我想这有用 这可绝了
I think it works, dude. that was pretty specific.
那泰迪熊 这三明治
The teddy bear, the sandwich…
我刚刚想了这个。
I'm guessing this.
我刚刚想说
I'm guessing that.
那么 这样的事一定会一直发生
Well, that definitely goes on the list.
我们该怎么办 你说呢
What are we supposed to do, huh?
阻止人们的愿望实现
Stop people's wishes from coming true?
听起来像是要干件蠢事
Sounds like kind of a douche-ey thing to do.
是啊 也许是 但是试试吧 老哥
Yeah, maybe. but come on, man.
这种事一定是要付出什么代价的
When has something like this ever come without a price tag?
并且通常是致命的
And usually a deadly one.
我不知道 这真他妈是个好吃的三明治
I don't know. it's a damn good sandwich.
好吧
All right. fine.
那我们先保留这个愿望直到我们搞清状况
We'll put a hold on the wishing till we figure out what's going on.
嗯 先生们
Uh, gentlemen, gentlemen.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我们这里不允许吃自带的食物
We don't allow people to eat outside food here.
但是我不想吃这里的东西
Well, i am certainly not gonna eat the inside food here.
卫生局
Health department.
你 我的朋友 这里有鼠患
You, my friend, have a rat infestation.
根据56号应急处理措施我们要关闭这里
We're gonna have to shut this place down under emergency hazard code 56c.
老鼠
Rats?!
就是个喷泉 石膏雕塑的
Typical fountain, plaster buddha.
我什么也没看到
Nothing I can see.
是啊，什么也没有
Yes, nothing.
我们把这里打扫得很干净
We keep a clean place here.
先生
Sir,
我要求你在初期调查期间离开这里
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave during the preliminary investigation,
好吗
Okay?
谢谢合作
Thank you.
你想试试吗
Oh, come on.Aren't you a little bit tempted?
不
No.
不会是真的 我不信这一套
Wouldn't be real. I wouldn't trust it.
我不清楚 可泰迪熊貌似是真的
I don't know. that bear seemed pretty real.
是啊
Yeah.
如果你能回到过去 重新开始
Come on, if you could wish yourself back, you know, before it all started…
想像一下 你能做你的律师
Think about it … you'd be some big yuppie.
有车有房
Lawyer with a nice car and a white picket fence.
我不想那样
Not what I'd wish for.
当真
Seriously?
现在说回去已经太晚 迪恩
It's too late to go back to our old lives, dean.
我已经不是以前的萨姆了
I'm not that guy anymore.
好吧 那你想要什么
All right, well, what, then? hmm? what would sammy wish for?
莉莉丝 人头落地
Lilith's head on a plate.
很血腥
Bloody.
好吧
Okay.
那是什么
What is that?
某种古硬币 我不认识这图案
Some kind of old coin. I don't recognize the markings.
该死
Damn.
腿也用上力
Lift with your legs.
可能是那个小猩猩焊上的
Is that little mother welded on there?
这是什么
Hey, hey, hey, what is this?!
这样会搞坏我的喷泉
You are gonna break my fountain!
先生 按规定我不该打你 可我还是会打
Sir, i don't want to slap you with a 44/16, but I will.
很好 谢谢
All right, thanks.
看看这个 我有个办法
Let me see that. I got an idea.
该死
Damn!
硬币有魔力
Coin's magical.
确实有
Boy, i'd say.
这泉可能有邪神保佑
I think it's hoodoo that's protecting the well.
我想我们弄不坏
I don't think we can destroy this.
好了 你仔细看看这个
All right, here. you got to look into this.
你去哪儿 我突然想起了什么
Where you going? something just occurred to me.
- 怎么 - 别担心 夫人
- What? - Don't worry, ma'am.
我是卫生部的
I'm with the health department.
你可以自由切换
So, you can turn it on and off, huh?
你怎么知道我
How … how did you know that I was…
实际上你是到许愿井那里投了个硬币
You actually walked up to a wishing well, dropped a dime,
想要变得隐形 好偷看女的洗澡
And wished to be invisible so you could spy on women in the shower?
不是
N-no. no.
不是 那不可能
N-no, no, no. that's crazy.
把裤子穿上
Put on some pants.
别隐形
And stay visible.
好吧
Okay.
你们最好快跑
You better run!
你有问题吗 先生
You got a problem, mister?
什么 没有
What? no.
迪恩
Dean?
你没事吧
You all right?
愿望变质了 萨姆
The wishes turn bad, sam.
非常坏
The wishes turn very bad.
三明治 对吧
The sandwich, huh?
那硬币是巴比伦时代的
The coin was babylonian.
它被诅咒了
It's cursed.
我找到了些零碎的传说
I found some fragments of a legend.
我很好
I'm good.
这个
The, uh…
硬币上面的蛇叫提亚玛特
The serpent is tiamat.
是巴比伦的原生混乱之神
Which is the, uh, babylonian god of primordial chaos.
当时他们的神父可能在研究黑魔法
I guess their, uh, priests were working some serious black magic.
他们造的硬币
They made the coin?
是的 为了撒播混乱之种
Yeah, to sow the seeds of chaos.
你投硬币并对着许愿池许愿时
Whoever tosses a coin in the wishing well, makes a wish,
池就会被激活
It turns on the well.
所有的愿望都会成真
Then it starts granting wishes to all comers.
但是愿望都会被扭曲 你想要个说话的泰迪
But the wishes get twisted. you ask for a talking teddy…
它就会给你个病熊
You get a bipolar nut job.
你则得到了大肠杆菌
And you get e. coli. mm.
几百年来 这东西已经搞乱了不少城镇
This thing has turned more than one town upside down over the centuries.
有些甚至从地图上彻底消失
It's even wiped a few off the map.
我是说 一个人许愿 会有些麻烦
I mean, one person gets their wish, it's trouble,
每个人许愿 就是灾难
But everybody gets their wish… it's chaos.
有办法阻止它吗
Any way to stop it?
有一个
Yeah. one way.
我们得找到第一个许愿的人
We got to find the first wisher.
第一个投硬币许愿的人
Whoever dropped the coin in and made the first wish,
能取回硬币 收回愿望
They're the only ones who can pull it back out and reverse the wishes.
现在来看 只实现了几个愿望
So for now, we've got a couple of nutso dreams come true,
可一旦许愿池的事传播开来
But once the word gets out about the well,
情况就会越来越糟
Things are just gonna get crazier and crazier.
迪恩 醒醒
Dean, wake up!
怎么了
What?
起来了
I'm up.
什么事
What?
睡得好吗
Sleep well?
挺好
Yeah.
倒下 睡着 然后精神饱满
Tan, rested, and ready.
迪恩 拜托 老哥 你以为我看不出来吗
Dean, come on, man. you think I can't see it?
看出了什么
See what?
做噩梦 还酗酒
The nightmares, the drinking.
我跟你可是形影不离的
I'm with you 24/7.
我知道一定有什么事困扰你
I know something's going on.
萨姆 求你了
Sam, please.
尤瑞尔没有说谎 但你有说
Uriel wasn't lying, but you are.
你记得地狱的一切 对吗
You remember hell, don't you?
你想从我这儿知道些什么 嗯 什么
What do you want from me, huh? what?
真相 迪恩
The truth, dean.
我的意思是 我是你弟弟 我希望你至少能对我倾诉
I mean, i'm your brother. I just wish you'd talk to me.
你得小心许愿
Careful what you wish for.
很好笑
Cute.
行了 我们可以停下这种夫妻关系治疗法的对话行吗
Come on, can we stow the couples therapy, huh?
我们还有事儿要做 我想要做点儿事
We're on a job. I want to work.
你找到了些什么
What do you got?
求你了
Please?
我们这儿有泰迪熊 中彩票强人 还有能隐身的变态
We got teddy bear, uh, lottery guy, invisible pervert guy.
他们全部都应该在最近两周里去许过愿
They all must have wished sometime in the last two weeks.
但谁是第一个
But who wished first,
以及他什么时候许的什么愿 我们就不得而知了
And how are we supposed to know who else wished for what when?
那么 当它们被公布到报纸上时就容易多了
Well, it helps when they announce it in the paper.
追溯到一个月前
Goes back a month.
韦斯利·蒙代尔和
Wesley mondale and ms.
赫普·林恩·凯西女士宣布了他们令人吃惊的婚讯
Hope lynn casey have announced their surprise engagement.
噢 真爱
Ah, true love.
对我们而言是条好消息
Best lead we got.
韦斯 你睡着了吗
wes, are you sleeping? hmm?
噢 不
Oh, uh, no.
没 没有 我只是 嗯 我只是闭目养神而已
No, no. I was just, um … I was just resting my eyes.
我想你会想要点点心
I thought you might want a snack.
赫普 你不需要做这些的
Oh, wow, hope, you didn't have to do that.
我喜欢
I wanted to.
好吧 不 我
Well, no, i…
我必须这么做
I had to.
因为我爱你胜过一切 亲爱的
Because I love you more than anything, lover.
是啊
Yes.
嗯 赫普 坐下来行吗
Um, hope, sit down, okay?
好的 韦斯
Yes, wes.
赫普 你快乐吗
Hope, uh, are you happy?
我爱你胜过一切
I love you more than anything.
我知道
I know.
我也同样爱你
And I love you.
非常地爱
Very much.
这也是为什么我希望你做事的前提是
That's why I want you to start doing.
这件事要是能让你快乐的事
Things that make … that made you happy before.
当然 韦斯 我会试着快乐起来的
Yes, wes, I'll try to be happier.
我马上就做
I'll start right away.
不 不 不 我不是那个意思
No, no, no, that's not what I mean.
- 我是说 - 噢 韦斯 求你了
- I…I'm talk - Oh, wes, please.
别生我的气
Please don't be angry with me.
你知道 我会立刻改 立刻改 马上改
You know, i'd just die, I'd just die, i'd die!
不 不 不是 我 我没有生气
No, no, no. don't … I'm … I'm not angry.
我没有生气
I'm not angry!
没有
No.
那么让我挑起你的欲火 韦斯
Then let me make it up to you, wes.
给我改过自新的机会
Let me make it right.
不 不 我 我
No, no, i'm … I'm…
我去开门
I'll get it.
韦斯
Wes!
你居然没告诉我你叫了筹备婚礼的花商来
You didn't tell me that you called the florists for the wedding.
你真是太好了
You're the best! mmm! ah!
我去拿我准备那一打资料来
I'm gonna go get my folders.
嗯 好的
Uh, Okay.
韦斯利 过得怎样
Wesley, how's it going?
应该是韦
It's "we…
斯
S-s."
- 你们俩不是卫生部门的吗 - 是的
- Aren't you the guys from the health department? - Yeah.
也算是花商
And florists on the side.
以及FBI
Plus fbi.
- 在星期四 我们还是泰迪熊医生 - 什么
- And on thursdays, we're teddy bear doctors. - Huh?
我们是谁并不重要 重要的是我们所知道的
Doesn't matter who we are. what matters is what we know.
看来你是硬币收藏家 韦斯
So, coin collector, huh, wes?
噢 是的 我的
Oh. yeah. my…
祖父留给我的这些硬币
Grandfather gave them to me.
最近有没有丢失过一枚呢
Did you happen to lose one of those coins lately?
而丢失呢
And by "lose,
我是指在幸运陈饭店的许愿池里抛硬币许愿
" I mean drop into a wishing well at lucky chen's and make a wish on it?
没有 我不懂你们所说的
No, i … I don't know what you're, uh, talking about.
好吧 现在
Okay, now.
我有很多打算 但是咧
I have a lot of ideas, but, you know,
我们没有那么多钱
We don't have all the money in the world.
韦斯目前正在失业中
Wes is between jobs right now.
有更多的时间陪我
Means more time for me.
知道吗 我打算弄日本花道似的婚礼
You know, i'm thinking a japanese-ey ikebana kind of thing.
好极了 我能想象出来
Yes. I can see it. yeah.
能说说你们俩是怎么遇到的吗
So, hope, uh, tell us how you two lovebirds met.
- 那是我生命中最美好的一天 - 我猜也是
- Oh, best day of my life. - I bet.
对啊 最好玩的是
Yeah! it's the funniest thing.
我们都在这儿长大 但我却不认识他
We both grew up here, but I never really knew who he was.
甚至连名字都不知道
Not by name anyway.
直到上个月的某一天
Until one day last month,
貌似是我第一次注意到他
It was like I just I just saw him for the first time.
他是那样的耀眼
He was just…glowing.
那样的鲜明
Oh, just glowing.
宝贝儿 给我们煮点咖啡好吗
Uh, babe, can you get us some coffee?
愿意效劳
Yeah, anything, yeah.
可以了
Oh. okay.
去吧
Okay.
好了
够了
Oh, okay.
可以了
Oh. mm-mm, okay.
去吧 可以了
Okay. okay.
去吧 去吧
好的
Yeah.
韦斯 我们都知道了
Wes, we know.
说出真相吧
So tell us the truth.
二战的时候
My … my grandfather found the coin in north africa, you know,
我祖父在北非发现了这些硬币
World war ii.
然后带了回来
And, uh, he brought it back.
他说这是真正的许愿币
He, um, he said it was a real wish-granting coin,
但谁都不曾用过
But that nobody should ever use it.
它是我的全部 在爷爷死后 我就想
It was all I had, and when he died, i thought, "well, you know what?
为什么不拿来试试呢
Why not give the coin a shot?"
好吧 现在你就许个让硬币回来的愿望
Yeah, well, now you're gonna wish it back.
不要 我才不要呢
Ha ha, no, i'm not.
如果你不停下这一切 噩梦即将降临
If you don't stop it, something bad's gonna happen.
噩梦 就如我们
Something bad … like us.
真切的希望你能跟我们走一趟
We really wish you'd come with us.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我的愿望成真
So, my wish came true.
怎么就会成为噩梦呢
Why does that have to be a bad thing?
因为愿意早已南辕北辙了 韦斯
Because the wishes go south, wes.
小镇已经陷入疯狂
Your town is going insane.
行了
Come on.
坐那儿 跟我们说说
You're gonna sit there and tell me that your.
你愿望进行程度 你许了什么愿望
Relationship with hope is functional, that it's what you wished for?
我希望她爱我胜过一切
I wished she would love me more than anything.
是吗 结果怎样
Yeah, and, uh, how is that going?
对你有利吗
That seem healthy to you?
比她之前忽视我要好很多
Well, it's a hell of a lot better than when she didn't know I was alive.
你不可能得到想要的一切 伙计 不像现在这样
You're not supposed to get what you want, man, not like this.
没人能这样
Nobody is.
硬币能掌控你的欲望
That's what the coin does.
也能反噬你的心智
It takes your heart's desires and it twists it back on you.
听说过《小心你许的愿》系列吗
You hear of the whole "be careful what you wish for"?
刚刚撞到什么了吗
Did we just hit something?
我啥也没看见啊
I didn't see anything.
小心你许的愿
"careful what you wish for."
知道是谁说的吗
You know who says that?
像你们这种外表好看的笨蛋
Good-looking jerks like you guys,
就因为碰巧帅了点才那么容易钓辣妹
The ones who've got it so easy because you happen to be handsome.
- 容易 - 容易
- Easy? - Easy?
是呀 女人看上过你们对吗
Yeah. women … women look at you, right?
她们也注意过你们
They notice you.
相信我们 远没那么简单
Believe us, we do not have it easy.
我们悲惨的很 从未得到过自己想要的
We are miserable. we never get what we want.
事实是
In fact,
我们不得不拼尽全力和命运做斗争
We have to fight tooth and nail just to keep whatever it is we got.
但知道吗 也许那才是问题关键 韦斯
But you know what? maybe that's the whole point, wes.
人毕竟只是人 他们是悲哀的动物
Yeah, people are people 'cause they're miserable bastards,
从未得到过他们真正想要的
'cause they never get what they really want.
对极了 得到了想要的 你就疯了
Right, yeah, you get what you want, you get crazy.
看看迈克尔·杰克逊或是哈塞尔霍夫
Take a look at michael jackson, hmm? or hasselhoff.
知道吗 现在愿望偏爱上我了 彻底的
You know what? hope loves me now … completely.
感觉棒极了
And it's awesome.
另外 看看周围
Besides, look around.
说到哪啦？你们这群家伙在谈论精神病？
Where's all this, uh, insanity you guys were talking about?
只管按下按钮
Just hit the button!
得去保护他们
Well, that should cover it.
向托德下跪
Kneel before todd!
住手
Stop it!
收到
Fine!
我来对付托德 你带韦斯利去幸运陈饭店
I'll handle todd. you get wes to lucky chen's.
出发
Go!
走
Right.
小子
Hey, kid!
能和你小谈一会吗？
Can I talk to you for a second?
让路！滚开！
Get out of my way!
行 你看 我能 托德
Okay. hey, I can dig it, todd.
这 这难道是托德
It … it's todd, right?
瞧我 我知道这情况
Look, i-i know the score.
- 好吧 他们 - 他们每天都在欺负你
- Okay? they're… - They're bullying you. every day.
是的 你永远不会知道那是什么滋味
Every day! you do not know what it's like!
对我真得不知道 你是你 我是我 所以没法阻止他们
No, no, i don't. but, you know, you're you and I'm me, so couldn't stop them.
做任何事情
to keep doing anything.
然后 奥德丽 埃尔默告诉了我愿望实现了
Then audrey elmer told me the wishing well worked.
够了 够了 你看 我懂了
Okay, okay. look … look, i get it.
他们是不是有点混蛋了
They're … they're mean little jerks, huh?
可是他们不是像你一样得超人啊
But they're not superhuman like you.
要知道 能力越大 越什么来着
You see, with great power comes great, great … ohh!
那 那 那个小孩随随便便就掀翻了一辆车
That … that … that kid turned over that car like … like it was nothing.
你已经已经看到泰迪熊了
You should have seen the teddy bear.
游戏时间结束 又要重新开始了
Now, come on. fun's over. time to pull the coin.
韦斯利
Wes!
若是这样，为什么不能只得到想要得呢
Well, why can't we just get what we want?!
这就是生活，韦斯
Because that's life, wes.
有愿望
Hope?
貌似我不得不做咯
I had to do it, didn't i?
他想让你许愿我们分开
He was gonna make you wish away our love.
小子
Hey, kid!
我真得不想这么做
I didn't want to have to do this.
你想死人啊
You wished a man dead?
我爱你胜过一切
I love you more than anything.
别说了
Stop saying that.
打住
Stop it!
但 我真得爱你
But I do.
胜过一切
More than anything.
甚至我自己
More than me.
你是我得一切
More than life.
韦斯
Oh, wes.
请别恨我
Don't hate me.
一切都会好得
It'll be okay.
我会让它好起来
I'll make it okay.
会没事得
It's gonna be okay.
恩 我相信你
Okay.
听我指挥你绝不会再有问题了
Follow my lead and you won't have a problem.
来啊
Come on.
行 但是朋友这就够了好不
Okay, man, no more! no more, okay?
如果我是你我绝不会和这个小子胡搅蛮缠
I wouldn't mess with this kid any more if I were you.
靠后
Stay back!
愿望
Hope.
我认识你
Do I know you?
应该没问题了
It shouldn't cause any more problems.
奥德丽得父母从巴厘岛回来了
Audrey's parents are back from bali.
好像愿望全部没用了
Looks like all the wishes are gone.
我们也是
And so are we.
稍等一会
Hang on a second.
啊
What?
你是对的
You were right.
关于什么
About what?
我不该对你说谎
I shouldn't have lied to you.
我想起了在地狱里发生什么事了
I do remember everything that happened to me in the pit.
全部
Everything.
那就告诉我吧
So tell me about it.
不行
No.
我保证不再说谎
Uh… I won't lie anymore.
我不打算谈论这个
But I'm not gonna talk about it.
迪恩 兄弟 你不能独自承担这一切
Dean, look, you can't just shoulder this thing alone.
一定要让我帮你
You got to let me help.
怎么帮
How?
一点点贴心得谈话 互爱互助就足够了
Do you really think that a little heart-to-heart, some sharing and caring,
有什么不同吗
Is gonna change anything?
怎么让我好起来？
Somehow…heal me?
此刻我可不想谈这些个晦气事
I'm not talking about a bad day here.
我了解
I know that.
我所看到的
The things that I saw…
语言无法形容
…there aren't words.
无法忘却
There is no forgetting.
无法抹去
There's no making it better.
因为是我切切实实的感受
Because it is right here…
永远的伤痕
Forever.
你永远不会了解
You wouldn't understand.
我也永远没办法让你了解
And I could never make you understand.
所以 不是我不想 对不起
So I am sorry.